Guide to the Martha Wilson Papers, 1950-2021 (bulk 1964-2006) MSS.175
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Subject Files, 1960-2011; 3 DVDs; 700 Megabytes in one computer disc.
  - Subseries C: Loose Documents including Productions/Scripts/Works by others
    - 3 Women in Black - Women in Black Zine, Undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - 15 Minutes 2000, Undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - 45 John St. Memorabilia 9/2004 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Address and phone directory, ca. 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - ACLU Arts censorship project, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - The Andy Warhol Foundation for the Visual Arts, 1994-1997 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - The Angel Project annotated, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Architectural plans for Dean Street, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Archive, Image, Text: The Myth and Realities of What Archives Hold - course description, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Art Work 1971-1974 for NYFA application, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Artists Space cards, Undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Artists: What/Now? conference, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Ashley Robert, I The Park. VII The Backyard, Undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Astroflash horoscope, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Astrology 4/16/97, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Avant-garde Art and Literature Conference - Hofstra University, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Bachhuber, Liz - Office Life, Undated (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - BAF Final Panel Visual Arts, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Ballonzoli, Joelle - King of the Roastbeef's Effectiveness is Matchless, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Biographical info for Martha Wilson, Undated (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Book Performance - May 1st, 1985, Skuta (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Brooklyn College letterhead, Undated (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Business Cards, 1971-2005 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Business Cards, 1971-2005 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Calendar, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - [Chapter 3 of Grace], Undated (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - The Circus Amok Activity and Coloring Book, Undated (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Collection of stamps, Undated (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Colo, Papo, Undated (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Comley Art, 1989-2002 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Conversations: Onajide Shabake, Carol Sun, Linda Matalon, Molly Blieden, 1996-1997 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Deflecting the Blind Spot - Suzy Lake and Martha Wilson, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - [Dietario 1985 from] Brown envelope 1/2 (Box 102)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      This item must be used in tray provided. Researchers can turn pages but must maintain the order of interfiled papers within. Handle with care.
    - Disband (from box labeled correspondence 1978-1985) (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Disband Reunion Dinner, Undated (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Disc and CD Rom, Undated (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Documentation, Whitney performance, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Dominic, Magie, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Downtown Little League, 2000-2001 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Drawing on Napkin, ca. 1988 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - El International Restaurant, 1986 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Flux-Mass, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Fortune Cookie Fortunes, Undated (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - Franklin Furnace Documents, 1979-2006 (Box 100, Folder 20-21)
    - Franklin Furnace Documents, Declaration of Martha Wilson, 1989 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Franklin Furnace Documents, undated (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Franklin Furnace Documents, Martha Wilson Dollars, undated (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Franklin Furnace Flue, Vol.2, Num.1, annotated, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Fusco, Coco, ca.1998 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - George School Alumni Award Speech, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Glashuasser, Suellen, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Golub/Spero by Susan Harris, 1993 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Gordh, Bill Gettin' Tired, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Gordh, Bill Two Months (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Graves, Nancy; Pedro Cuperman, Tango, undated (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Grolier Club Membership, 1981-1982 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Harte Lyon, Else Bret Franklin Furnace: A Tragedy, undated (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Helin, Yvette, The Pedestrian Project, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Hicks, Janet, Bargain Prices, 1981 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Honorariums and Performances, 1976-2005, undated (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - A knock at the door, 2004 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Lacy, Suzanne - Cancer Notes, Undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - L, Dinh Q. and Moira Roth - From Vietnam to Hollywood, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Lolita, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Looking for Jiro, Tina Takemoto - video recording, 2011; 1 DVD (Box Shared Fales 007)
    - M.R. - From Far Away, A Cycle of Poems, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Maranda, Michael - Faking it in Cyberspace: Boys will be Girls will be Boys, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Martha Wilson address book discards, 1985-1995 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Martha Wilson interview, annotated, Undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Martha Wilson interview by Patrick Moore, annotated, Undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Materials from Alabama, Florida, Louisiana, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Materials from envelope labeled American Museum of Natural History, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Membership cards, Undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Miksic, Vesna - Hear-T, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Misc. documents ca. 1963 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Misc. loose documents, 1965-1968 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Misc. loose documents, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Misc. loose documents, 1998-2003 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Misc. loose documents, Undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Misc. loose documents, Undated (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Misc. loose documents, Undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Misc. loose documents, Undated (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Misc. loose documents, Undated (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Miss Vera's Academy Award, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Montano, Linda - Art/Life Institute Handbook, Undated (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Moulton, Charles - Bicycle Billboard, Participatory Performance, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - [Moulton] - Performance- The conference of unconditional surrender (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - NEA Onsite Evaluator, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - New Observations Magazine - edited by Wilson, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - New Observation Magazine notes, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - NYC Downtown Book Sidebar Text, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - NYC Messenger Calendar for 1990 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Notecards designed by MW, c.1975 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Notes and Annotations, 1968-1970 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Notes and Annotations, ca. 1975-1987 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Notes and Annotations (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Notes and Annotations (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Notes and Annotations, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Notes and Annotations, ca.1997-2000 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Notes and Annotations, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Notes and Annotations, ca.2000 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Notes and Annotations, ca.2001 (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Notes and Annotations, ca.2002 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Notes and Annotations, ca.2004-2005 (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - Notes and Annotations, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - Notes and Annotations, undated (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - Notes and Annotations, undated (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - Notes and Annotations, undated (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Notes and Annotations, undated (Box 35, Folder 46)
    - Notes and Annotations, undated (Box 35, Folder 47)
    - Notes removed from books, 1998-2001 (Box 35, Folder 48)
    - On the needs of Visual Artists Roundtable, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 49)
    - Outside the Frame, preliminrary exhibition checklist, 4/8/93 (Box 35, Folder 50)
    - Performances 1985-1986, ca.1986 (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - Performance 1994-1996, 1994-1999 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Performance Notes, 1990-1998 and undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Para Research Natal Horoscopes, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - From envelopes labeled Perf Res., ca. 1996-1997 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Photocopies of Idiom A, a journal of feminist Post-Totalitarian Criticism, undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Photographs, c. 1968-1970 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Photographs, Comley, 1998-1999 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Photographs, performances, 1984-1996 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Photographs, Undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Photographs, c. 1975 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Political Art Documentation and Distribution: The PADD Archives, 1993-1994 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Powell, William - datebook, a permanent calendar, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Princeton University - School of Architecture - office copy, Undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Reading and the Arts of the Book - Draft for Mel Edelstein, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Real Art Products, Undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Reviews of Lisa Weger and Jim Reva - No Place Like Home, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Roth, Moira - Cyber Theater of Mneme and Melete, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Roth, Moira - Linda Montano, Seven Years of Living Art, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Roundtable 2: Impossible Archives, Annotated, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Sarah Palin and Tina Fey on SNL, fall 08 - video recording, 2008; 1 DVD (Box Shared Fales 007)
    - A Short Story about Nova Scotia, Undated (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Skowhegan School Awards Dinner and Speech, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Skowhegan School Awards Dinner, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Sondheim, Alan, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - South, Frank - Push Here annotated, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Subversion - Preliminary checklist, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Summer exhibition: Outdoor Sculpture, Merriwold West Gallery, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Tickets, Undated (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Tickets, Undated (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Tipper Gore's advice for the 90's, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - [Travel and other receipts from] Brown envelope 2/2, Undated (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - University of North Carolina - Chapel Hill Fine Arts Festival, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - Unsoeld Seminar Series, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - Van Horn, Erica - Scraps of an Aborted Collaboration, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - Videostory, Undated (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - Weis, Cathy - A String of Lies press kit, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - What are you Voting For comic, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - Writing Sales, c. 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - Written for WNYE Show on history of performance art, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Subseries D: High School, College, and Graduate School Education
    - High school papers and homework assignments, 1960-1964 (Box 86, Folder 15-17)
    - Religion, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - Chemistry, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - Comparative Literature, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - English, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - Evolution Botany, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 44)
    - Philosophy, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - untitled notebook, 1965-1966 (Box 36, Folder 46)
    - General Zoology, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Introduction to Government, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 48)
    - Physics Notebook #1, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - Physics Notebook #2, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - untitled notebook, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - untitled, undated ca. 1966 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - American College Seminar, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - English 324, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - College Notebook and Journal, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - The Novel, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Bible 201, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Romantic Literature, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Untitled Notebook, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - papers from college, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - African Art, undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - English Language, undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Europe since 1816, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - General Zoology, undated (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Untitled Notebook, undated (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Untitled Notebook, undated (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Untitled Notebook, undated (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Collected Papers, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - College Notebook (1970-1971), n.d. (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - College Papers. October 16, 1969-March 25, 1970, 1969-1970 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Wilmington, Yearbook of Wilmington College, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Papers from College. December 10, 1970 - April 5, 1971, 1970-1971 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - College Papers - April 7, 1972-February 7, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - The Subverted Comic Pattern in American Fiction - M.A. Thesis, Dalhousie University, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - The Subverted Comic Pattern in American Fiction - M.A. Thesis, Dalhousie University, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Untitled notebooks, undated (Box 87, Folder 1-5)
  - Subseries E: Birth of Comly
    - Baby Career, Undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Baby Shower (1 of 3), 1989 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Baby Shower (2 of 3), 1989 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Baby Shower (3 of 3), 1989 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Baby Shower photos, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Materials from gift bag of Comly's first Birthday, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Subseries F: Comly's schoolwork
    - Washington School 1992-1994 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Comly Wilson Kindergarten 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - P.S. 234 1994-1995 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Comly Wilson Kindergarten, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Comly Wilson first grade, 1995-1996 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Comly Wilson - 2nd Grade, 1996-1997 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Comly Art, 1996-1997 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Comly Wilson - 3rd Grade, 1997-1998 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Comly Wilson, 1999-2000 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - P.S. 234 Graduating Class, 1999-2000 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Class 602, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Comly Wilson - Math, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Homework, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Humanities, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Spanish, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Untitled Folder, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Untitled Folder, ca. 2000 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Student Planner, 2000-2001 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - American History, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Extra Mail, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Spanish, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Student Planner, 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Wilson, Comly, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Language Arts, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Math, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Notes, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Science, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Social Studies, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Student Planner, 2002-2003 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Comly, undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Comly File, undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Comly - Middle School, undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Comparing and Scaling, undated (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Class 602 Math, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Flash Cards, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Loose Documents from Comly Folder, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Math, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - untitled notebook, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Music, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Subseries G: Poconos House [RESTRICTED], undated
    - Upper Black Eddy RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Meridian Bank CD 2/14/87 RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - York Federal RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Dean Witter Salary Reduction Plan RESTRICTED, Undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Poke (1 of 3) RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Poke (2 of 3) RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Poke (3 of 3) RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Mortgage etc. RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - MW + SC Agrm't RESTRICTED (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Bell of PA RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Holiday Poconos RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - PP + L RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Insurance RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Manuals and Warrantees RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Area Info RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Mauch Chunk Trust Co. Biz RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Receipts 87 RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Poconos Repair and clmp. RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Loose documents from Poconos box RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Untitled folder RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - GMC Jimmy 1986 RESTRICTED, undated (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Subseries H: Fifth Avenue Loft
    - Brooklyn Reno Contracts, undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Rent Bills Building Expense, 1982-1992 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - David Spiker, 1988-1995 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Restricted materials from David Spiker, undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Brooklyn 32-33 Fifth Ave., undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Series IV: Juvenilia, 1950-1967
  - Subseries A: Drawings, Artifacts, Awards, etc.
    - Camp Betsy Cox Subject Folder, ca. 1964 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - art awards, ca. 1955 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - untitled folder of drawings and notes, ca. 1960-67 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - comps, 1967- undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Diary, ca. 1964 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - from folder- Drawings Martha (includes notes and letters), ca. 1950-1960 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Martha's Hair, Fall 1956 Age 8 1/2 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Martha's teeth, undated (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - from folder, Drawings Martha (includes notes and letters), ca. 1950 - 1960 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - loose documents, 1955-1961 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Subseries B: School and Yearbooks
    - Council Rock Jr.-Sr. High School Yearbook, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - School Report Letters, 1953-1956 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Junior Grammar Drills, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Social Studies History Notes, in 7th Grade, Mr. Sawiks, 410 AD - 1800, undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Materials from 1962-1963 Student Directory (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - 1962-1963 George School Student Directory (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Physics Class Notes 9/20/64, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Atoms at your service book report, [1964] (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - English Class Notes, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - French Class Notes, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - history class notebook undated, [1964] (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - History Class Notebook, [1964] (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - History Notes Freshman Year, Mr. Hansen, From Java Man thru W.War I, undated (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - French Class Notebook, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - French Class Notebook 12/64 - 5/65, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - High School Notebook (multi-subject), undated (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - School Notebook, undated (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - School Notebook, undated (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - School Notebook, undated (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - High School Mathematics Unit 1, undated (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - High School Mathematics Unit 2, undated (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - High School Mathematics Unit 3, Undated (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - George School yearbook, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - George School yearbook, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - George School yearbook, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - George School yearbooks, OPUS 1965 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - George School High School Diploma, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - A Man and a School, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 27)
- Series V: Medical and Financial Files [RESTRICTED], 1995-2009
  Series V is described at the box level.
  RESTRICTED
  - Medical and Financial Files [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 60)
  - Medical and Financial Files [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 61)
  - Medical and Financial Files [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 62)
  - Medical and Financial Files [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 63)
  - Medical and Financial Files [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 64)
  - Medical and Financial Files [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 65)
  - Medical and Financial Files [RESTRICTED], undated (Box 66)
  - Medical and Financial Files [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Box 89, Folder 4-10)
  - Medical and Financial Files [RESTRICTED], 1995-2009 (Box 90, Folder 1-8)
- Series VI: Flyers, Invitations and Programs, 1975-2013
  The Flyers, Invites and Programs in Series VI were loose in boxes with other materials when they arrived at Fales. They have been foldered and arranged at the box level, roughly by date span.
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 1975-1985 (Box 44)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 1985-1987 (Box 45)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 1988-1990 (Box 46)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 1989-1994 (Box 47)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 1994-1996 (Box 48)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 1994-1995 (Box 49)
  - Flyers, Invites, Programs, and Posters, 1998 (Box 67)
  - Flyers, Invites, Programs, and Posters, 1998-2000 (Box 50)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 2000-2002 (Box 51)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 2002-2003 (Box 52)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 2003-2005 (Box 53)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 2005-2006 (Box 54)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 2006-2008 (Box 55)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 2007-2008 (Box 56)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 2006-2012 (Box 93, Folder 1-23)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 2008-2012 (Box 91, Folder 1-24)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 2010-2012 (Box 88, Folder 1-9)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 2010-2013 (Box 94, Folder 1-22)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, 2011-2013 (Box 92, Folder 1-20)
  - Flyers, Invites, and Programs, undated (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 20)
- Series VII: Clippings, Articles and Magazines, 1968-2012
  The Clipping, articles and weeklies in Series VII were loose in boxes with other materials when they arrived at Fales. They have been foldered and arranged at the box level, roughly by date span.
  - Subseries A: Clippings by Year
    - Clippings, 1968-1992 (Box 57)
    - Clippings, 1993-2008 (Box 58)
    - Clippings, 1989-2012 (Box 86, Folder 18-19)
  - Subseries B: Articles
    - Articles, 1991-2006 (Box 59)
  - Subseries C: Magazines
    - High Performance, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 23)
    - New Observations, 1989, 1993 (Box 94, Folder 24)
- Series VIII: Objects, 1960-2005
  - Willmington College Box, 1960-1967 (Box 68, Object ID: 175.2.0001)
    Shoebox of memoribilia from Wilmington College and the George Schholl. Two autograph books and assortred letters, pamphlets etc.
  - Paper plate with inscription, undated (Box 69, Object ID: 175.2.0002)
  - Blue box with handle, ca. 1983 (Box 69, Object ID: 175.2.0003)
    A collection of epherma and memorobilia including clippings, maps and materials related to Franklin Furnace.
  - Box with egg and invitation inside, 1987 (Box 69, Object ID: 175.2.0004)
  - Painted box with bow and objects inside, undated (Box 69, Object ID: 175.2.0005)
  - Gold painted shoe with invitation inside, undated (Box 69, Object ID: 175.2.0006)
  - Pink plastic heart shaped box with glitter and tape measure inside, undated (Box 69, Object ID: 175.2.0006)
  - White florist box labeled O.O.C. with inscription and objects inside, 1980 (Box 69, Object ID: 175.2.0008)
  - Paper airline labeled U.S. Clap, undated (Box 69, Object ID: 175.2.0009)
  - Red charm with bell, Undated (Box 69, Object ID: 175.2.0010)
  - Placard with a screw design, undated (Box 69, Object ID: 175.2.0011)
  - Purple garter with flower, undated (Box 69, Object ID: 175.2.0012)
  - Franklin Furnace pencil, undated (Box 72, Object ID: 175.2.0013)
  - Small glass object, undated (Box 72, Object ID: 175.2.0014)
  - Art Parade 3D glasses, 1983 (Box 72, Object ID: 175.2.0015)
  - Pair of children's shoes, undated (Box 72, Object ID: 175.2.0016)
  - Skowhegan Governors Award in box, 1991 (Box 72, Object ID: 175.2.0017)
  - Small plastic baby doll, undated (Box 72, Object ID: 175.2.0018a)
  - Small plastic and fabric fan (Box 72, Object ID: 175.2.0018)